Hello everyone, welcome back to another great lesson here with us at EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎回到EnglishPod的另一堂精彩课程。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
And I'm Erika.
我是Erika。
And today we're going to be getting money.
今天我们要去取钱。
That's right.
没错。
We're going to have a lesson about the ATM.
我们将上一堂关于ATM的课。
The ATM or?
ATM或者？
Automatic Teller Machine.
自动柜员机。
Okay, that's what it stands for, ATM.
好的，这就是ATM的全称。
So we're going to be looking at the language that you'll probably find in an ATM maybe
所以我们要看看你在ATM上可能会遇到的语言，也许
in the United States or in English speaking country.
在美国或英语国家。
That's right.
没错。
But before we begin, why don't we look at some vocabulary that we'll hear in the dialogue.
但在开始之前，我们先看看对话中会听到的一些词汇。
Vocabulary Preview.
词汇预览。
As we mentioned, the ATM or Automatic Teller Machine is a machine where you get your money,
正如我们提到的，ATM或自动柜员机是一种取钱的机器，
right?
对吧？
Exactly.
没错。
And also, well, some people are in different places, they may call it the bank machine.
而且，嗯，有些地方的人可能叫它银行机。
Yeah, or maybe the cash machine.
是啊，或者现金机。
Or just a money machine or something.
或者就叫取款机之类的。
All right.
好的。
So ATM.
所以是ATM。
ATM.
ATM。
And now let's take a look at our next word.
现在让我们看看下一个词。
Local Authorities.
地方当局。
The Local Authorities.
So what are the Local Authorities?
那么地方当局是什么？
Well, basically, it's the police.
嗯，基本上就是警察。
The police.
警察。
Why do you say local authorities?
为什么说地方当局？
Okay, well, authority is the person in charge, right?
好的，嗯，authority就是负责人，对吧？
The boss.
老板。
So the local authorities are basically the people who are the boss of this place.
所以地方当局基本上就是这个地方的负责人。
In that area.
在那个区域。
Yeah.
是的。
So the police.
所以就是警察。
The local authorities.
地方当局。
So why don't we start now with our dialogue?
那我们为什么不现在开始我们的对话呢？
Why are we talking about local authorities and ATM machines?
我们为什么要谈论地方当局和ATM机？
I don't know.
我不知道。
We got to listen to find out.
我们得听听看才知道。
Stupid girl making me spend so much money.
那个傻姑娘让我花这么多钱。
Now I have to get it from the ATM.
现在我只好从ATM取钱。
Hello, welcome to Universal Bank.
您好，欢迎来到环球银行。
Please insert your card into the slot.
请将您的卡插入插槽。
I know where to put my card.
我知道卡往哪儿插。
Stupid machine talking to me like I'm an idiot.
傻机器跟我说话，好像我是白痴一样。
Please input your six digit PIN code followed by the pound key.
请输入您的六位PIN码，然后按井号键。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Please select an option.
请选择一个选项。
Thank you.
谢谢。
You have selected withdraw.
您已选择取款。
Yeah, yeah, I know what I selected.
是，是，我知道我选了啥。
Just give me my money.
快给我钱。
Please type the amount you would like to withdraw.
请输入您想取款的金额。
Thank you.
谢谢。
You want to transfer.
您想转账。
10,000 US dollars to the World Wildlife Foundation.
一万美元给世界野生动物基金会。
If this is correct, please press one.
如果正确，请按一。
No, no, stupid machine.
不，不，傻机器。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
No.
不。
Confirmed.
已确认。
Thank you for using our bank.
感谢您使用我们的银行。
Please remove your card from the slot.
请从插槽中取出您的卡。
Goodbye.
再见。
No way.
不会吧。
What happened?
发生什么事了？
Give me my money.
给我钱。
Danger.
危险。
The exits have been sealed and the doors will remain locked until the local authorities
出口已被封锁，门将保持锁闭，直到地方当局
arrive.
到达。
Thank you for using our bank.
感谢您使用我们的银行。
Have a nice day.
祝您愉快。
No.
不。
All right.
好吧。
So it's not his day today.
所以他今天运气不好。
I think he was very unlucky and maybe he's going to be in trouble.
我觉得他很倒霉，可能要有麻烦了。
I know.
我知道。
And he was on a date.
而且他还在约会。
This is probably one of the worst things that can happen to a guy when he's on a date.
这大概是男人约会时可能遇到的最糟糕的事情之一。
All right.
好吧。
Yeah.
是的。
So well, we saw some of the language that was related to an ATM, money and banking.
那么，我们看到了与ATM、钱和银行相关的一些语言。
So why don't we take a look at that now in Language Takeaway.
所以我们现在在“语言要点”环节来看看这些。
Language Takeaway.
语言要点。
All right.
好的。
So the guy had to insert his card into the slot.
所以那个人必须把卡插入插槽。
Okay.
好的。
So slot.
所以是slot。
Slot.
slot。
All right.
好的。
Slot.
slot。
And that is an opening, right?
那是一个开口，对吧？
Or a type of hole maybe.
或者一种洞。
Yeah.
是的。
It's a hole that is usually long.
通常是一个长形的洞。
Long and it's like a rectangular hole.
长形的，像一个长方形的洞。
Yeah.
是的。
A slot is never a circle.
slot从来不是圆形的。
Okay.
好的。
So for example, when you get mail, the mailman will put it into your mailbox through the
所以比如，你收信时，邮递员会把信放进你邮箱的
slot.
投信口。
That's right.
没错。
Okay.
好的。
And now that he put his card into the slot, he had to input a six digit pin code.
现在他把卡插入插槽后，必须输入一个六位PIN码。
Want to just do both together?
要不要一起讲？
Digit and pin code?
digit和pin code？
Yeah.
是的。
Okay.
好的。
So a six digit pin code.
所以是六位PIN码。
All right.
好的。
Now we have two words here that are new.
现在我们有两个新词。
Digit.
digit。
Digit is basically a number between zero and nine.
digit基本上就是0到9之间的一个数字。
Okay.
好的。
So any number between zero and nine is considered a digit.
所以0到9之间的任何数字都算一个digit。
Yes.
是的。
So 100 is made up of three digits.
所以100由三个digit组成。
Three digits.
三个digit。
Okay.
好的。
And what about pin code?
那pin code呢？
A pin code is your secret number that you use to take money out.
pin code是你用来取钱的秘密号码。
Now why wouldn't we say password?
为什么我们不说password？
Password is usually letters.
password通常是字母。
Okay.
好的。
And pin code is numbers.
而pin code是数字。
Exactly.
没错。
All right.
好的。
He had to input his six digit pin code and then after that, he had to press the pound
他必须输入他的六位PIN码，然后之后，他必须按井号
key.
键。
Pound key.
井号键。
Now this is strange.
这有点奇怪。
A pound key.
井号键。
What is that?
那是什么？
Well, you know on a phone, on the bottom right, there's a key or a button that looks like
嗯，你知道电话上，右下角有一个键或按钮，看起来像
a number sign.
一个井号。
Number sign.
井号。
So kind of like two vertical lines and two horizontal lines.
有点像两条竖线和两条横线。
Yeah.
是的。
Two lines going up and down, two lines going across.
两条上下线，两条横线。
Okay.
好的。
So that's called the pound key.
所以那叫井号键。
All right.
好的。
What about the other one?
那另一个呢？
It's called the star.
叫星号。
The star.
星号。
Star key.
星号键。
The star key.
So he's got the pin code after the pound key.
所以他在井号键后输入了PIN码。
Now he's ready to withdraw money.
现在他准备取款。
So we heard withdraw.
所以我们听到了withdraw。
Okay.
好的。
So withdraw is?
所以withdraw是？
Is a noun.
是名词。
It's the action of taking money out.
是取钱的动作。
Okay.
好的。
A withdrawal.
取款。
Okay.
好的。
And to withdraw.
而to withdraw。
To withdraw is just the verb.
to withdraw是动词。
To take out money, right?
取钱，对吧？
Exactly.
没错。
So we have the noun and the verb.
所以有名词和动词。
The only difference is an L at the end.
唯一的区别是末尾的L。
Yes.
是的。
So withdraw noun and withdraw verb.
所以withdraw名词和withdraw动词。
Okay.
好的。
And well, he wanted to withdraw money, but something happened with the ATM and it turned
嗯，他想取钱，但ATM出了点问题，结果
out that he was going to transfer money.
他要转账。
So transfer.
所以是transfer。
Transfer.
transfer。
When you transfer money, you take it from one place and put it in another.
当你转账时，你把钱从一个地方转到另一个地方。
Okay.
好的。
And usually in banking, when you transfer money, you don't really see it, right?
通常在银行业务中，转账时你实际上看不到钱，对吧？
Exactly.
没错。
It's all electronic.
都是电子的。
So you just put it from one bank account to another, but you never actually see this money.
所以你只是从一个银行账户转到另一个，但从未真正看到这些钱。
Exactly.
没错。
So you transfer money.
所以是转账。
Transfer.
transfer。
And now this one also has a verb and a noun, right?
这个也有动词和名词，对吧？
Right.
对。
A transfer.
一次转账。
And to transfer.
和转账。
Same word.
同一个词。
Yep.
是的。
Easy.
简单。
All right.
好的。
So why don't we listen to our dialogue for the second time.
那我们为什么不第二次听我们的对话呢？
It's going to be slowed down a little bit, and then we'll come back and look at some
它会稍微慢一点，然后我们回来看看一些
phrases.
短语。
Stupid girl making me spend so much money.
那个傻姑娘让我花这么多钱。
Now I have to get it from the ATM.
现在我只好从ATM取钱。
Hello.
您好。
Welcome to Universal Bank.
欢迎来到环球银行。
Please insert your card into the slot.
请将您的卡插入插槽。
I know where to put my card.
我知道卡该放哪儿。
Stupid machine talking to me like I'm an idiot.
破机器，跟我说话像我是个白痴似的。
Please input your six digit PIN code followed by the pound key.
请输入您的六位PIN码，然后按井号键。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Please select an option.
请选择一个选项。
Thank you.
谢谢。
You have selected withdraw.
您已选择取款。
Yeah, yeah.
行了，行了。
I know what I selected.
我知道我选了啥。
Just give me my money.
赶紧给我钱吧。
Please type the amount you would like to withdraw.
请输入您想取款的金额。
Thank you.
谢谢。
You want to transfer.
您想转账。
$10,000.
一万美元。
Two.
两。
The World Wildlife Foundation.
世界野生动物基金会。
If this is correct, please press one.
如果正确，请按一。
No, no.
不，不。
Stupid machine, what are you doing?
破机器，你在搞什么？
No.
不。
Confirmed.
已确认。
Thank you for using our bank.
感谢您使用我们的银行。
Please remove your card from the slot.
请从插槽中取出您的卡。
Goodbye.
再见。
No way.
没门。
What happened?
发生什么事了？
Give me my money.
把我的钱给我。
Danger.
危险。
The exits have been sealed and the doors will remain locked until the local authorities
出口已被封锁，门将保持锁闭，直到当地警方
arrive.
到达。
Thank you for using our bank.
感谢您使用我们的银行。
Have a nice day.
祝您愉快。
No.
不。
Okay, so that was a little easier to understand.
好吧，那部分稍微好懂一点。
But Marco, there's some interesting phrases here, some instructions that you commonly
但是Marco，这里有一些有趣的短语，一些你在使用银行机器时经常
read or hear when you're using a bank machine.
读到或听到的指示。
So why don't we take a look at these phrases in Fluency Builder.
那我们不如在流利度构建环节看看这些短语。
Fluency Builder.
流利度构建。
Well, the bank machine told this guy to insert your card.
嗯，银行机器让这家伙插入卡片。
Insert your card.
插入您的卡。
So this verb, to insert, to place inside.
所以这个动词，insert，意思是放入内部。
Exactly.
没错。
So what else can we insert?
那我们还能插入什么？
Well, for example, commonly you insert a disc.
嗯，比如，通常你会插入一张光盘。
Yeah, in your computer.
对，在你的电脑里。
In your computer, right?
在你的电脑里，对吧？
Yep.
是的。
Or you insert a CD into your CD player.
或者你把CD插入CD播放器。
Or DVD into your DVD player.
或者DVD插入DVD播放器。
Yep.
是的。
All right.
好的。
So to insert something, to put inside.
所以insert something，就是放进去。
Yes.
对。
So he had to insert his card into the slot.
所以他得把卡插入插槽。
And then the bank machine asked him to select an option.
然后银行机器让他选择一个选项。
Select an option.
选择一个选项。
Now this is a very common phrase that you will not only see in ATMs, but basically everywhere,
这是一个非常常见的短语，你不仅会在ATM上看到，基本上到处都有，
right?
对吧？
On computers or the internet or many, many things where you're dealing with machines.
在电脑或互联网上，或者很多很多跟机器打交道的地方。
So it's an order that says, well, select one of these choices that you have.
所以这是一个指令，意思是，嗯，从你有的这些选择中选一个。
Make a choice.
做个选择。
Yeah.
对。
Select an option.
选择一个选项。
All right.
好的。
So two simple phrases, but very useful and also very high frequency, right?
所以两个简单的短语，但非常有用，而且使用频率也很高，对吧？
Yeah.
对。
And you know what?
你知道吗？
When you use phrases like these two, it sounds quite professional, doesn't it?
当你用像这样的短语时，听起来挺专业的，不是吗？
Yeah.
对。
A little bit formal.
有点正式。
Okay.
好的。
So why don't we listen to our dialogue for the last time and then we'll come back and
那我们最后再听一遍对话，然后回来
talk a little bit more.
再聊一会儿。
Stupid girl making me spend so much money.
傻女孩让我花这么多钱。
Now I have to get it from the ATM.
现在我只好去ATM取钱。
Hello.
你好。
Welcome to Universal Bank.
欢迎来到环球银行。
Please insert your card into the slot.
请将您的卡插入插槽。
I know where to put my card.
我知道卡该放哪儿。
Stupid machine talking to me like I'm an idiot.
破机器，跟我说话像我是个白痴似的。
Please input your six digit PIN code followed by the pound key.
请输入您的六位PIN码，然后按井号键。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Please select an option.
请选择一个选项。
Thank you.
谢谢。
You have selected withdraw.
您已选择取款。
Yeah, yeah.
行了，行了。
I know what I selected.
我知道我选了啥。
Just give me my money.
赶紧给我钱吧。
Please type the amount you would like to withdraw.
请输入您想取款的金额。
Thank you.
谢谢。
You want to transfer $10,000 to the World Wildlife Foundation.
您想转账一万美元到世界野生动物基金会。
If this is correct, please press one.
如果正确，请按一。
No, no.
不，不。
Stupid machine.
破机器。
What are you doing?
你在搞什么？
No.
不。
Confirmed.
已确认。
Thank you for using our bank.
感谢您使用我们的银行。
Please remove your card from the slot.
请从插槽中取出您的卡。
Goodbye.
再见。
No way.
没门。
What happened?
发生什么事了？
Give me my money.
把我的钱给我。
Danger.
危险。
The exits have been sealed and the doors will remain locked until the local authorities
出口已被封锁，门将保持锁闭，直到当地警方
arrive.
到达。
Thank you for using our bank.
感谢您使用我们的银行。
Have a nice day.
祝您愉快。
No.
不。
All right, Erica, so what about you?
好了，Erica，那你呢？
Have you ever had any problems with the ATM?
你用过ATM出过问题吗？
I've had more problems than I can count.
我遇到的问题多得数不清。
What happened?
发生什么事了？
Well, I think in the last two years, I've probably lost about seven bank cards in an
嗯，我想在过去两年里，我大概在ATM里丢了七张银行卡。
ATM.
Really?
真的吗？
You forget it in the slot?
你忘在插槽里了？
Yes.
对。
I leave it in the slot and then walk away from the bank machine and no bank cards.
我把它留在插槽里，然后走开，卡就没了。
Well, I think now the ATMs, because this is a common problem, now they have like a little
嗯，我想现在的ATM，因为这是个常见问题，它们会有一个小
alarm that when you take out your money and everything, it just starts beeping and beeping
警报器，当你取完钱什么的，它就开始哔哔响，
until you take out your card.
直到你拿走卡。
Yes.
对。
And I like the bank machines that actually give you your card first and then give you
我喜欢那种先给你卡再给你钱的银行机器。
your money.
Because if they give me my money first, that's all I want, right?
因为如果它先给我钱，那才是我想要的，对吧？
So I run away with my money and leave my card in the bank machine.
所以我拿着钱就跑，把卡留在机器里。
Right.
对。
I think that's a good idea.
我觉得那是个好主意。
I've never seen it before, though.
不过我从没见过。
In Switzerland, they have them like that.
在瑞士，他们就有那样的。
In Switzerland.
在瑞士。
And I think it's the ATMs that you only have to swipe your card.
而且我觉得那是只需要刷卡的ATM。
Oh, yeah.
哦，对。
I've done that as well and also ruined a bank card with that.
我也那样做过，还因此弄坏了一张银行卡。
I swiped it too many times, put in the wrong pin code and...
我刷了太多次，输错了PIN码，然后……
It blocks your card.
卡就被锁了。
Yeah.
对。
Terrible.
太糟了。
Well, what about you guys?
嗯，你们呢？
I'm sure everyone has some experience or some inconvenience with ATM machines.
我相信每个人都有一些跟ATM打交道的经历或不便。
So why don't you come to our website and tell us all about it?
所以不如来我们的网站，跟我们说说吧？
You can also find lots more resources on our website to help you learn English.
你还可以在我们的网站上找到更多资源来帮助你学英语。
So check it out.
去看看吧。
And until next time, goodbye!
下次再见，拜拜！